# Uladzislau Nazarau



vladnew91@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/uladzislau-nazarau-5b8ab6190

### Summary

Welcome. My name is Uladzislau. I have more than 2 years JavaScript experience. My assignments involved working with React, React Hooks, Typescript, Redux. I am also fluent in Git, Redux-Saga, Material-Ui. My current English level is B1. You can find some of my pet-projects on my GitHub. Have a nice day!

### **Experience**

### **GW** Frontend Developer (React)

**Aheadworks** 

Apr 2022 - Present (2 months +)

#### Responsibilities:

Development and addition of new functionality in existing and new projects using React and its ecosystems. Fixing apps and Aheadworks modules. Solving technical problems (support tasks), apps and modules arising from users Aheadworks.

## Frontend Developer

Startup

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022 (7 months)

Stack: React, React Hooks, Redux, Typescript, Redux-Saga, Material-Ui.

I have done:

- 1. Sign-in page (layout, authorization, validation, result processing);
- 2. Forgot password page (layout, validation, result procesing);
- 3. Entities page (layout, show list, CRUD operations);
- 4. Statistics page (visualize data to charts use Recharts library, switch data by periods: hour, day, week, mounth, year, filter data by users);
- 5. Settings page (layout, validation, change: initials, mail, passwords); and other.

### Education



#### **Belarusian State University of Transport**

Bachelor's degree, Real estate engineer 2009 - 2014

### **Licenses & Certifications**

Frontend, JavaScript - The Rolling Scopes School

Issued Feb 2021 - Expires Aug 2021

## Skills

React • Redux • Redux-Saga • React Hooks • Git • Figma (Software) • Material-UI • TypeScript